What else do we have? Let me remove this layer as well. What else do we have? We have create with AI so we have the image generator we just used
We have AI headshot
So we can take an image of ourselves and then convert that image. It's it's also very funny
So we're gonna use this as well, but I don't want to explain it for now
We have AI in a AI artifacts. We have AI expand AI replace old photo restorer
What else a lot of them? So colorize black and white photo. You know if you have an old photo a black and white photo
This option will allow you to convert it to a colored photo
automatically so artificial intelligence will do that for you
We also have watermark remover
That can also be useful as well. We have grab text
What else do we have? Oh, so this will provide us with the ability to this will provide us with the ability to
Take a certain text out of a an image and then be able to
Edit it, you know, it's very weird because all of these things these weren't available available
Impossible the previous years when it came to the design industry, but these are all the power of artificial intelligence
What else do we have? We can blur background. We can change background. We can add up an AI background
We can change clothes. We can cut out face
You know as you see as a cute sticker or whatever
We can change the hairstyle of a certain image
we can use the AI recolor rare so we can change the color of a certain thing and
Instant flash as well as HDR
So these are all the AI tools available